
- Royal green hojari frankincense - Drink as toyah/tea - kills viruses, detoxes DNA of viruses, rearranges DNA back to original state

ABOUT WEED -ENDOCANCABINOID SYSTEM IS LINKED TO NEURO SYSTEM AND IMMUNE SISTEM. SMOKING INJECTS CANABINOIDS INTO THE BODY AND THROWS OFF REGULATION OF THESE 2 SYSTEMS Creates a blockage


		ABOUT HERBS - Clove - high in magnesium, kills tapeworms Oregano - high in magnesium Red reishi mushrooms - has polysaccharid beta 133 gluten , attaches to the cancer cells, reproduces T cells and helps fight aids, Frankincense (black frankincense)- (medical grade frankincense) drink as tea/detoxes body. Royal green hojari frankincense - Drink as toyah/tea - kills viruses, detoxes DNA of viruses, rearranges DNA back to original state GINGER REPAIRS DNA ALSO Dandelion greens - good for you Asparagus should only be eaten raw!!! Potatoes and asparagus have asparagine - by cooking asparagine creates a acrylamide which is toxic to blood  
https://www.lifepathscounseling.com/holistic-health/